https://www.oceanlinkinc.com/privacy-policy/

401-683-4434Info@OceanLinkInc.comBrandsServicesRequest for ServiceCommissioningRefit ServicesFuel PolishingAbout UsAffiliationsTestimonialsContact UsDirectionsUpcoming EventsNewsletter 0 Items Privacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email addresses, phone number, payment information, billing/shipping addresses. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)To improve our websiteTo improve our customer serviceTo process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.To send periodic emailThe email address you provide for ordering processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect you information?We implement a variety of security measure to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.Do we use cookies?We reserve the option to use cookies in our website.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, to protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Online/Offline Privacy Policy This privacy policy applies to information collected through our website and to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://www.oceanlinkinc.com/terms-and-conditions/Your ConsentBy using our site and/or engaging in offline transactions, you consent to our privacy policyChanges to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.This policy was last modified on 3/9/2017Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.Ocean Link Inc One Maritime Drive #10 Portsmouth, RI 02871 (401)-683-4434 info@oceanlinkinc.comProduct CategoriesSelect a categoryAir ConditioningBoat Care ProductsFresh Water SystemsFuel SystemsHeating SystemsMarine LightingMarine TanksMarine Tanks & Tank PartsOdor Control ProductsPlumbing PartsPortable Fuel TanksPumpsSanitation SystemsTank PartsToilets & Sanitation SystemsUncategorizedWater HeatersWatermakers / Reverse OsmosisWatermakers R/O Store Search Search for:
Search Site Search Search for:
CartIf You Are Ordering A Waste Water TankPlease Download Our Ordering Instructions: Waste Water Tank Ordering Instructions Click HERE for Tank Installation Parts
One Maritime Drive, Suite #10Portsmouth, RI 02871
